>> HI. I'M MAGGIE Q FROM NIKITA,
AIRING FRIDAYS THIS FALL ON
THE CW.
>> AND I'M KRISTOFFER POLAHA
FROM THE CW'S LATEST
AND GREATEST RINGER,
SURE TO BE YOUR NEW FAVORITE
SHOW ON TUESDAYS THIS FALL.
>> AND WE'RE HERE TO--
>> WE'RE HERE TO TEACH YOU SOME
SERIOUS MARTIAL ARTS MOVES.
THEY'RE THE KIND OF MOVES YOU'RE
GONNA NEED TO MASTER IF YOU
WANNA BE PREPARED FOR PRIMETIME.
>> ACTUALLY, KRIS, I THINK
WE'RE HERE TO PRESENT
THE CW 2011 FALL PREVIEW.
>> OH. UH, THAT TOO.
>> YEAH.
>> BUT--AND HOW TO DELIVER
A FULL-ON ROUNDHOUSE KICK.
[grunting]
HUH?
WAS THAT TOO MUCH?
>> IT WAS OKAY.
>> UH...
>> [laughs] WELCOME TO
THE CW 2011 FALL PREVIEW.
KRIS AND I WILL BE YOUR GUIDES
THROUGH ALL THE GREAT NEW
PROGRAMMING COMING THIS FALL
TO THE CW.
>> FROM THE UPPER EAST SIDE TO
THE OUTER LIMITS OF IMAGINATION,
FROM HIGH DRAMA TO HIGH ACTION,
THIS FALL THE CW HAS FIVE GREAT
NIGHTS OF PROGRAMMING, WITH NEW
EXPERIENCES GUARANTEED EVERY
NIGHT.
>> MONDAYS GET YOUR WEEKLY DOSE
OF ANGST AND BETRAYAL AT
AN EARLIER TIME WITH ALL-NEW
EPISODES OF GOSSIP GIRL,
FOLLOWED BY A NEW SERIES FROM
THE GOSSIP GIRL GURUS,
HART OF DIXIE.
RACHEL BILSON LEADS AN
OUTSTANDING ENSEMBLE CAST OF
GREAT CHARACTERS IN SMALL TOWN,
U.S.A.
>> AND KICK OFF TUESDAYS WITH
AN ALL-NEW SEASON OF 90210.
>> FOLLOWED BY THE RETURN OF
A TRUE TV STAR,
SARAH MICHELLE GELLAR,
IN A NEW DRAMA EVERYONE,
ESPECIALLY KRIS, IS BUZZIN'
ABOUT.
RINGER, A PSYCHOLOGICAL
THRILLER WHERE NO ONE IS WHAT
THEY SEEM.
REALLY?
>> MM.
>> [laughs]
>> ON WEDNESDAYS, IF YOU THINK
CELEBRITIES ARE EASY TARGETS,
MM-MM, YOU THINK AGAIN.
THE BOLD NEW REALITY SERIES H8R
BRINGS CELEBRITIES FACE-TO-FACE
WITH THEIR WORST CRITICS--YOU--
AND IT DOESN'T ALWAYS END
PRETTY.
>> UH-OH.
THEN AMERICA'S NEXT TOP MODEL
IS TAKING IT TO THE NEXT LEVEL
WITH THEIR FIRST EVER ALL-STAR
EDITION.
YOUR FAVORITE PAST CONTESTANTS
ARE GONNA BATTLE IT OUT,
NO-HOLDS-BARRED, TO SEE WHO
STILL HAS WHAT IT TAKES
TO BE QUEEN OF THE CATWALK.
>> THURSDAY IS A FULL-ON FRIGHT
FEST, NOT TO BE BELIEVED.
IT ALL KICKS OFF WITH NEW
EPISODES OF THE HIT SHOW
THE VAMPIRE DIARIES.
>> FOLLOWED BY A HOT NEW SERIES
FROM THE SAME TEAM THAT BROUGHT
YOU THE VAMPIRE DIARIES.
PREPARE TO BE BEWITCHED BY
THE SECRET CIRCLE.
>> OOH.
UH, WHICH BRINGS US TO FRIDAY,
THE MOST ACTION-PACKED NIGHT OF
THE WEEK, AS I'M SURE THAT
MAGGIE WILL AGREE.
NIKITA MAKES HER MOVE WITH
ALL-NEW EPISODES ON FRIDAY
NIGHT.
>> FOLLOWED BY ALL-NEW
GUARANTEED-TO-THRILL EPISODES
OF SUPERNATURAL.
>> FIVE DISTINCT NIGHTS OF
ALL-ORIGINAL, AWE-INSPIRING
PROGRAMMING.
YOU READY FOR THE RIDE?
>> I ALREADY BOUGHT MY TICKET.
WELCOME TO
THE CW 2011 FALL PREVIEW.
>> [laughs]
>> [grunts]
[explosion]
[energetic dance music]
&l &l
>> SHE'S LOCKED AND LOADED.
[LMFAO's Party Rock Anthem]
>> THANK GOD. SHOW TIME.
>> &l SHAKE THAT &l
>> HOLD ON.
>> ALL RIGHT, EVERYONE, LET'S
PARTY!
[cheering]
>> [hisses]
>> all: [screaming]
>> SOMEONE'S FEISTY.
>> &l PARTY ROCK IS &l
&l IN THE HOUSE TONIGHT &l
>> KEEP YOUR MODEL COMPOSURE!
>> LISTEN TO ME!
>> [screams]
>> OOH!
>> [sighs]
THIS HAS GOT TO END.
>> I THOUGHT IT JUST DID.
>> &l GET UP, GET DOWN &l
>> WE'RE GONNA HAVE A LITTLE
MORE DRAMA!
>> &l PUT YOUR HANDS UP &l
&l PUT YOUR HANDS UP &l
[explosion]
>> OHH!
>> [laughs]
>> &l JUST HAVE A GOOD, GOOD &l
&l GOOD TIME &l
>> THIS IS THE CREATION OF
A STAR.
>> BRILLIANT.
[chatter, laughter]
>> WE'RE GONNA HAVE SO MUCH FUN
TOGETHER.
>> &l SHAKE THAT &l
>> YOU KNOW THOSE PEOPLE WHO
HAVE EVERYTHING FIGURED OUT?
>> WELL, DR. ZOE HART IS ABOUT
TO LEARN THE PITFALLS OF HAVING
PLANNED TOO MUCH TOO SOON.
>> FROM BIG CITY SURGEON TO
RURAL SOUTHERN DOCTOR, RACHEL
BILSON LEADS AN AMAZING ENSEMBLE
CAST IN A SHOW FILLED WITH
GREAT CHARACTERS, HUMOR, AND
AND A WHOLE LOT OF HEART.
>> CW'S PROUD TO PRESENT
HART OF DIXIE.
>> SEE THE NEW YORKER THAT
DOESN'T QUITE FIT IN?
THAT'S ME, DR. ZOE HART.
I'M ON A BUS IN THE MIDDLE OF
NOWHERE.
BUT I GUESS I SHOULD START AT
THE BEGINNING.
I GRADUATED FROM MEDICAL SCHOOL
AT THE TOP OF MY CLASS.
>> DR. HART?
MY NAME IS DR. HARLEY WILKES.
I'M FROM BLUEBELL, ALABAMA.
I'D LIKE TO OFFER YOU A JOB.
>> THANKS. YOUR OFFER IS REALLY
SWEET, BUT I HAVE A PLAN.
BYE.
I HAD IT ALL--THE MOST AMAZING
BOYFRIEND WHO WAS JUST AS DRIVEN
AS I WAS.
BEST PART WAS, WE LANDED IN THE
SAME RESIDENCY PROGRAM.
AND THEN I SUNK TO MY LOWEST
POINT.
FIRST, THE MAN I LOVED DUMPED
ME.
SECOND OF ALL--
WHAT DO YOU MEAN I DIDN'T GET
THE CARDIOTHORACIC FELLOWSHIP?
WHAT DO I NEED TO DO TO GET NEXT
YEAR'S CT SPOT?
>> IF YOU WANT MY
RECOMMENDATION, SPEND THE NEXT
12 MONTHS AS A GENERAL
PRACTITIONER.
>> THERE ISN'T A SINGLE G.P. JOB
IN THIS WHOLE CITY.
>> THERE ARE OTHER PLACES TO
PRACTICE MEDICINE BESIDES
NEW YORK.
>> I WAS LOST.
EVERY FELLOWSHIP WAS TAKEN.
I HAD PUT ALL MY EGGS IN THE
WRONG BASKET.
AND THEN I SAW IT.
ANOTHER POSTCARD FROM THAT
SOUTHERN GUY, HARLEY.
"REAL BUSY. COULD USE AN
EXTRA-TALENTED HAND."
DR. WILKES, YOU WIN.
I'M ON MY WAY.
>> CAN I OFFER YOU A RIDE,
MA'AM?
SO LET ME GUESS--NEW YORKER.
I LIVED IN TRIBECA FOR A WHILE.
>> I'VE BEEN EXILED FROM
MANHATTAN.
THIS IS MY PURGATORY.
>> IF YOU CONSIDER PURGATORY
TO BE A PLACE WHERE NEIGHBORS
TAKE CARE OF EACH OTHER AND
EVERY THIRD TUESDAY DEMANDS
A PARADE, YOU CAN CALL IT WHAT
YOU WANT, BUT I CALL IT HOME.
I'M GEORGE TUCKER.
>> ZOE.
DR. ZOE HART.
>> WELL, GOOD LUCK, DR. ZOE
HART.
I HOPE YOU FIND WHAT YOU'RE
LOOKING FOR.
>> HI. IS DR. WILKES AROUND?
>> ARE YOU ZOE HART?
>> YEAH.
>> HARLEY PASSED AWAY.
>> BUT WHY WOULD HE WANT ME TO
SHOW UP IF HE WAS DEAD?
>> HARLEY LEFT YOU HIS PRACTICE.
THE THING IS, HARLEY ONLY LEFT
YOU HALF THE PRACTICE.
HE SHARES IT WITH DR. BREELAND.
>> WHOA.
>> DR. HART, THE BELLES ARE
ELITE YOUNG LADIES.
>> "THE BELLES"?
>> THEY'RE MEANER THAN THEY
LOOK.
>> I HEARD THERE WAS A NEW LADY
DOCTOR IN TOWN.
YOU ARE JUST SO PRETTY!
>> ZOE, THIS IS LEMON BREELAND.
>> OH, OKAY.
YOU'RE BRICK'S DAUGHTER.
IT'S REALLY NICE TO MEET YOU.
I'M DYING TO TALK TO YOUR DAD.
>> IF I WERE YOU, I'D BE GONE
BY THE TIME THAT HE RETURNS.
GOOD DAY.
[chuckles]
>> NOTIFY THE TOWN CRIER.
I'M OPEN FOR BUSINESS.
MABEL, THOSE DARK PATCHES ON
YOUR FACE...YOU HAVE MELASMA.
>> BRICK'S HERE.
>> WE HAVEN'T MET.
HI. I'M DR. ZOE HART.
HARLEY LEFT HIS HALF OF THE
PRACTICE TO ME.
>> I'M NOT GONNA SHARE THIS
OFFICE, NOT FOR ONE MINUTE.
>> I BELIEVE I CAN DO SOME GOOD
HERE.
>> THINGS HAVE BEEN WORKING JUST
FINE HERE IN BLUEBELL.
AND BELIEVE YOU ME, ZOE HART,
WE ARE GONNA CHASE YOU AWAY
FROM OUR WATERS.
>> MRS. H. ARRANGED FOR ME TO
STAY AT THE MAYOR'S PLANTATION.
>> YOU MUST BE ZOE.
>> NO WAY!
YOU'RE THE MAYOR?
LAVON HAYES, THE LINEBACKER?
>> WELL, LET ME SHOW YOU TO YOUR
QUARTERS.
>> YOU BEING THE MAYOR HERE IS
THE FIRST THING ABOUT BLUEBELL
THAT I ACTUALLY LIKE.
[both chuckling]
>> YEAH!
HERE IT IS.
YOU SHARE A GENERATOR WITH
WADE KINSELLA.
IF YOU GOT YOUR CURLING IRON
GOING WHILE HE GOT HIS AC ON,
COULD BE TROUBLE.
>> WELL, MY NIGHT HAD QUICKLY
GONE DOWNHILL.
YOU OVERHEATED THE GENERATOR.
>> NICE NIGHTGOWN.
I'M WADE.
>> THAT SMILE'S NOT GONNA WORK
ON ME.
>> WELL...IF YOU'RE NOT GONNA
BE POLITE, I'M NOT GONNA SHOW
YOU WHERE THE FUSE BOX IS.
[alligator growls]
>> [screaming]
>> WHEN SOMEBODY INTERRUPTS
THEIR NIGHTLY JOG TO CLIMB INTO
THE MUD TO SAVE OUR WELL-TONED
ASS, WE SAY THANK YOU.
>> WELL, THANK YOU.
>> SEE? SMALL TOWNS HAVE THEIR
PERKS, HUH?
>> I GUESS I'LL BE SEEING YOU
AROUND.
>> DID YOU SIGN OLD MAN
JACKSON'S EYE EXAM?
>> YEAH. WHY?
>> 'CAUSE HE JUST RAN GEORGE
OVER.
>> announcer: FROM THE CREATORS
OF GOSSIP GIRL.
>> I FEEL SO BAD.
>> WELL, YOU SHOULD!
HE NEARLY KILLED GEORGE TUCKER.
>> HEY, IF YOU WANTED TO SEE ME
AGAIN, YOU COULD'VE JUST ASKED.
>> IT'S MY--MY SHOULDER.
OW! WHAT THE HELL?
HAVE YOU NEVER HEARD OF BEDSIDE
MANNER?
>> WHY IS EVERYONE SO OBSESSED
WITH THAT?
>> BECAUSE IT'S NICE!
>> DR. HART, I DON'T FEEL WELL.
CAN YOU COME HERE, PLEASE?
>> I'LL BE THERE AS SOON AS I
CAN.
YOU'RE HAVING A BABY, AND YOU'RE
HAVING IT NOW.
I'M GONNA NEED YOU TO START
PUSHING, OKAY?
>> WHAT IS GOING ON HERE?
>> THIS BABY COMES OUT NOW,
OR WE LOSE BOTH OF THEM.
MRS. H, I NEED YOU TO HAND ME
MY SCALPEL.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> A SYMPHYSIOTOMY.
>> NO, I CAN'T LET YOU SLICE
OPEN HER PELVIS LIKE THAT.
THAT IS WAY TOO DANGEROUS.
>> WELL, WE HAVE NO CHOICE,
OKAY?
ARE YOU WITH ME?
>> I AM.
[newborn cries]
>> &l IF IT'S THE PRIZE &l
&l YOU'RE SEEKING &l
&l WELL, THAT AIN'T ME &l
&l AND IF YOU'RE THINKING &l
&l OF TRYING &l
&l WELL, THAT CAN'T BE &l
>> YOU JUST CAN'T LEAVE NOW.
YOU ASKED ME BEFORE WHY HARLEY
LEFT YOU HIS PRACTICE.
>> THAT'S MY MOM...
AND HARLEY?
>> HARLEY WILKES WAS YOUR
FATHER.
>> I'M STAYING IN BLUEBELL.
THEY COULD USE A GOOD DOCTOR.
I MAY NOT BE ONE YET, BUT MAYBE,
EVEN THOUGH YOU'RE GONE,
THERE ARE STILL SOME THINGS
YOU CAN TEACH ME.
AND FOLLOWING IN YOUR FOOTSTEPS
MIGHT HELP ME FIND MY WAY.
>> announcer: HART OF DIXIE.
SERIES PREMIERE--MONDAY,
SEPTEMBER 26th ON THE CW.
>> I LOVE IT WHEN A PLAN ALMOST
COMES TOGETHER.
>> ME TOO.
HART OF DIXIE AIRS MONDAYS
FOLLOWING GOSSIP GIRL THIS FALL,
ONLY ON THE CW.
>> AND THERE'S MORE OF
THE CW 2011 FALL PREVIEW WHEN
WE COME RIGHT BACK AFTER THIS.
OR WHEN WE COME BACK RIGHT AFTER
THIS--EITHER WAY.
>> HEY, MAGGIE, WHO DO YOU THINK
IS MORE HANDSOME--ME OR HIM?
>> SARAH MICHELLE GELLAR RETURNS
TO TV, BUT THIS TIME SHE'S ON
THE RUN FROM A SHADOWY PAST,
A PATH THAT LEADS HER RIGHT INTO
THE [indistinct] CASE OF
MISTAKEN IDENTITY.
>> AND YOU'LL NEVER GUESS WHO
THEY GOT TO PLAY HER IDENTICAL
TWIN.
WHAT?
>> MY NAME IS BRIDGET, AND I'M
AN ADDICT.
IT'S BEEN REALLY HARD TO STAY
CLEAN.
THINGS HAVE BEEN TENSE.
>> WE AGREE TO DROP THOSE
CHARGES IF YOU TESTIFY.
JUST GET UP ON THE STAND.
>> THAT'S WHAT I'M AFRAID OF.
NO ONE CAN PROTECT ME.
I FINALLY GOT A RESPONSE FROM
MY SISTER SIOBHAN.
SHE WANTS ME TO COME VISIT,
STAY AS LONG AS I WANT.
BUT RIGHT NOW IT'S THE ONLY
CHOICE THAT I HAVE.
[clock ticking]
I WAS WONDERING HOW YOU'D LOOK
AFTER SIX YEARS.
[clock ticking]
I MISSED YOU SO MUCH.
>> THIS IS OUR WEEKEND PLACE.
[clock ticking]
>> JUST LIKE MY HOUSE, EXCEPT
>> THIS IS OUR WEEKEND PLACE.
NOT AT ALL.
>> JUST LIKE MY HOUSE, EXCEPT
YOUR LIFE SEEMS PERFECT.
NOT AT ALL.
[echoing]
YOUR LIFE SEEMS PERFECT.
[clock ticking]
[echoing]
SIOBHAN!
[clock ticking]
OH, MY GOD.
SIOBHAN!
[clock ticking faster]
OH, MY GOD.
SIOBHAN KILLED HERSELF.
I SAW A WAY OUT, AND I TOOK IT.
[clock stops ticking]
I'M THE ONLY ONE THAT KNOWS
THAT SHE'S DEAD.
>> EVENING, MISS MARTIN.
>> EVENING.
THEY ALL THINK I'M HER.
THEY ALL THINK I'M SIOBHAN.
>> &l SEE THE SAFETY &l
&l OF THE LIFE YOU HAVE BUILT &l
>> BUT NO ONE'S LIFE IS PERFECT.
[elevator bell dings]
>> I'M WITH THE F.B.I.
>> &l THE GLASS YOU ARE ON &l
&l WHAT IF EVERYTHING &l
&l AROUND YOU &l
>> TONIGHT SEEMED SO HAPPY.
>> BUT THAT WAS AN ACT.
>> &l ISN'T QUITE AS IT SEEMS &l
>> OH, COME ON, SIOBHAN.
WE'VE SLEPT TOGETHER A THOUSAND
TIMES.
>> &l WHAT IF ALL THE WORLD &l
&l YOU THINK YOU KNOW &l
>> [echoing] HE'S NOT SAFE.
>> THIS IS YOUR GAME.
I'M JUST PLAYING BY THE RULES.
>> &l AN ELABORATE DREAM &l
&l &l
&l AND IF YOU LOOK AT &l
&l YOUR REFLECTION &l
>> SIOBHAN, WHAT DID YOU DO?
>> I KNOW WE NEGOTIATED,
BUT I WANT OUT.
>> &l ALL YOU WANT IT TO BE &l
>> YOU MUST SHARE YOUR SECRET.
>> &l WHAT IF YOU COULD LOOK &l
&l RIGHT THROUGH &l
>> I WONDER WHAT ELSE SHE'S
LYING ABOUT.
>> WHO ARE YOU?
>> WHERE THE HELL ARE YOU?
>> TELL ME WHAT'S GOING ON.
>> YOU HAVE THE WRONG GIRL!
[gunshot]
&l &l
[clock ticking]
[phone ringing]
[phone beeps]
HELLO?
>> SIOBHAN, WE HAVE A PROBLEM.
BRIDGET'S STILL ALIVE.
[clock ticking]
>> RINGER AIRS TUESDAYS
FOLLOWING 90210 THIS FALL
ON THE CW.
>> NOW, DON'T GO ANYWHERE.
THERE'S MORE OF THE CW'S NEW
FALL LINEUP TO COME WHEN
THE CW 2011 FALL PREVIEW
RETURNS.
>> YOU KNOW WHY THEY HIRED ME?
>> WHY?
>> 'CAUSE I'M A RINGER. HA!
>> [laughing] OH, MY GOSH.
>> THURSDAYS THIS FALL,
THE VAMPIRE DIARIES IS BACK,
FOLLOWED BY A NEW SERIES FROM
THE TEAM THAT BROUGHT YOU
THE VAMPIRE DIARIES.
>> THE MYSTERIOUS DEATH OF A
YOUNG GIRL'S MOTHER BRINGS HER
BACK TO THE TOWN HER MOTHER RAN
AWAY FROM, A TOWN WHERE NOTHING
IS WHAT IT SEEMS AND EVERYONE
HAS THEIR PART TO PLAY...
IN THE SECRET CIRCLE.
>> SOUNDS SPOOKY.
>> YEAH.
>> [chuckles]
[phone rings]
>> HELLO?
>> I GOT A FLAT.
>> ALL RIGHT, I'M COMING.
>> I KNOW HOW TO CHANGE A TIRE,
MOM.
MOM?
[static]
HELLO?
>> CASSIE?
[dramatic, suspenseful music]
&l &l
[screaming]
[gasps]
CASSIE.
[glass shatters]
>> announcer: A TRAGEDY CHANGED
CASSIE BLAKE'S LIFE FOREVER.
NOW SHE'S STARTING OVER IN THE
SMALL TOWN HER MOTHER LEFT
BEHIND.
>> CASSIE!
REALLY GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
>> HEY, GRANDMA.
>> announcer: AND SHE'LL SOON
DISCOVER THAT HER ARRIVAL WILL
BRING A TOWN'S DARK SECRET TO
LIGHT.
>> WE'RE HAPPY TO HAVE YOU HERE,
CASSIE.
I'M PRINCIPAL CHAMBERLAIN.
YOUR MOTHER WAS VERY SPECIAL TO
ME.
IF THERE'S ANYTHING THAT I CAN
DO TO HELP, YOU LET ME KNOW.
>> announcer: SHE'S MEETING A
NEW CIRCLE OF FRIENDS.
>> SO YOU'RE THE NEW GIRL.
>> YEAH. THAT'S ME.
>> TRY IT AGAIN.
>> HI. I'M DIANA.
>> I'M CASSIE.
>> EVERYBODY HANGS OUT AT THE
BOATHOUSE AFTER SCHOOL.
DROP BY, AND I'LL SHOW YOU
AROUND.
>> I SAW YOU AT SCHOOL TODAY.
HOW WAS YOUR FIRST DAY?
>> IT'S NOT OVER YET.
I'LL GET BACK TO YOU.
>> ADAM'S A HOTTIE.
AND HE REALLY DOES GO FOR THE
SAD, DELICATE TYPES.
>> announcer: AND HER TRUE
DESTINY IS ABOUT TO BE REVEALED.
>> I DON'T THINK SHE KNOWS
ANYTHING.
>> I THINK SHE NEEDS A NUDGE.
[engine fails to start]
>> LET ME OUT! HELP!
[screams]
>> PUT IT OUT.
>> I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHAT
HAPPENED.
>> YOUR CAR CAUGHT FIRE.
>> NO WAY. THAT WAS SOMETHING
ELSE.
THIS TOWN, IT'S A FREAKIN'
SIDE SHOW.
>> CASSIE, WAIT.
I THINK MAYBE I CAN HELP.
>> WHERE ARE WE GOING?
>> YOU'LL SEE.
IT'S OKAY, CASSIE.
[door squeaks open]
>> FINALLY.
>> HEY, NEIGHBOR.
>> OKAY, THIS IS GETTING REALLY
WEIRD.
>> YOU DON'T NEED TO BE SCARED.
>> THEN SOMEONE TELL ME WHAT'S
GOING ON.
>> WE'RE DIFFERENT.
YOU'RE DIFFERENT.
>> OH, FOR GOD'S SAKE!
SPIT IT OUT!
YOU'RE A WITCH.
YOU'RE A FULL-BLOODED,
100% WITCH.
WE ALL ARE.
>> THIS IS BEYOND CRAZY.
>> OUR ANCESTRY IS PART OF
A LEGACY THAT DATES AS FAR BACK
AS 1692.
>> YOU'RE SAYING I'M A WITCH?
>> LIKE YOUR MOTHER AND HER
MOTHER.
EACH FAMILY HAS A BOOK.
THE BOOK CONTAINS THOUSANDS OF
SPELLS.
WE'VE BEEN PRACTICING, BUT
WITHOUT A FULL CIRCLE, WE CAN
WE CAN ONLY DO REALLY LAME ONES.
>> COMPLETE CIRCLE IS SIX--
ONE FROM EACH OF THE SIX
FAMILIES.
>> YOU'RE THE SIXTH.
>> ARE THE CHILDREN PRACTICING?
>> IF THEY WERE PRACTICING, I
WOULD KNOW.
>> WE CAN'T LET IT HAPPEN
AGAIN.
>> OUR PARENTS HAD A CIRCLE
JUST LIKE OURS.
>> MY MOTHER WAS NOT A WITCH.
I WOULD HAVE KNOWN.
>> IT WAS ALL COVERED UP.
SOMETHING WENT WRONG.
PEOPLE WERE HURT.
SO THEY ABOLISHED WITCHCRAFT.
>> I DON'T BELIEVE YOU.
>> WITH CASSIE HERE, OUR POWER
IS MAGNIFIED LIKE 100 TIMES
OVER.
>> WE ARE DOING THIS MY WAY,
FAYE.
>> THAT SHIP HAS SAILED.
SKIES ABOVE, GIVE ME A SIGN.
>> DO NOT PUSH ME, FAYE.
I MEAN IT.
>> DO YOU WANNA TRY THAT AGAIN?
'CAUSE I DIDN'T QUITE BUY IT.
DID YOU?
[upbeat music]
&l &l
>> MY SWEET CASSIE...
YOU FINDING THIS MEANS I'M GONE
AND FOR THAT, I AM SO SORRY.
YOU HAVE INCREDIBLE POWER INSIDE
YOU.
>> ARE YOU DOING THIS?
>> WE ARE.
>> IT'S INCREDIBLE.
WHY DID MY MOM LEAVE HERE?
>> BAD THINGS HAPPEN WHEN YOU
MESS WITH FATE.
>> WHAT BAD THINGS?
>> YOU DRINK TOO MUCH, WHICH
MAKES YOU TALK TOO MUCH, AND I
CAN'T HAVE THAT.
THIS IS MY ONE AND FINAL
WARNING.
>> OH! OOH. SORRY.
>> ARE YOU...CASSIE BLAKE?
>> YES?
>> I WAS A GOOD FRIEND OF YOUR
MOTHER'S.
>> HEY. I SEE YOU MET MY DAD.
>> [gasps]
YOU AND YOUR TRICKS.
YOU DID THE RIGHT THING BRINGING
HER HERE.
SHE HAS THE GIFT.
>> ARE YOU SURE YOU CAN GET
CASSIE TO DO WHAT WE NEED?
>> I DON'T HAVE TO GET HER TO DO
A THING.
THE CIRCLE WILL TAKE CARE OF
THAT WITHOUT EVEN KNOWING IT.
>> FIND THE CIRCLE.
THE CIRCLE CAN PROTECT YOU.
>> MAKE IT STOP.
>> BELIEVE IN THE POWER OF THE
CIRCLE.
>> MAKE IT STOP.
>> BUT MOST OF ALL...
BELIEVE IN YOURSELF.
>> YOU DID IT.
YOU STOPPED IT, CASSIE.
YOU'RE ONE OF US.
>> I HOPED THAT KEEPING THIS
SECRET WOULD KEEP YOU SAFE, BUT
ALL I'VE DONE IS LEFT YOU
UNPROTECTED.
YOU HAVE INCREDIBLE POWER.
PEOPLE WILL COME FOR IT.
THEY WILL COME FOR YOU.
>> announcer: THE SECRET CIRCLE.
SERIES PREMIERE--THIS THURSDAY
AT 9:00, 8:00 CENTRAL ON THE CW.
>> DON'T MISS THE SECRET CIRCLE,
AIRING THURSDAYS FOLLOWING
THE VAMPIRE DIARIES THIS FALL--
>> ONLY ON THE CW.
>> HEY, LET'S TAKE A QUICK LOOK
INTO THE FUTURE AND SEE WHAT'S
COMING UP MID-SEASON.
>> FOR EIGHT YEARS,
ONE TREE HILL HAS FEARLESSLY
TACKLED EVERY TOPIC--ANGST,
BETRAYAL, LOVE TRIANGLES,
DIVORCE, ADDICTION, OBSESSION...
>> BUT THIS YEAR, IT TAKES ON
ITS BIGGEST STORYLINE YET.
>> THE CW PRESENTS
ONE TREE HILL, THE FINAL
SEASON.
>> GET DRESSED.
>> IS IT TRUE?
>> AH!
>> WE'RE PREGNANT.
[giggles]
>> [indistinct singing]
>> WE?
>> YOU AND ME.
>> THERE'S MORE EXCITEMENT
TO COME WHEN
THE CW 2011 FALL PREVIEW
RETURNS RIGHT AFTER THIS
SHORT BREAK.
>> [clears throat]
KRIS.
>> HUH?
>> KRIS, WE'RE--WE'RE BACK FROM
THE BREAK.
>> OH, HEY. UM, JUST A SEC.
SOME GUY ON MY TWITTER PAGE IS
POSTING VERY HURTFUL THINGS
ABOUT ME.
>> WELL, THEN YOU'D BE A GREAT
CANDIDATE FOR OUR NEXT SHOW,
H8R.
IT'S ABOUT CELEBRITIES WHO
CONFRONT THEIR WORST CRITICS--
YOU.
>> YEAH, WHY DOES EVERYONE GOTTA
BE A CRITIC, HUH?
>> THEY GO FACE-TO-FACE WITH
THE PEOPLE WHO LOVE TO TWEET,
BLOG, AND LOVE TO SPREAD THE
HATE.
>> WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK THEY'RE CALLED TROLLS,
AND I THINK THEY SUBSIST ON
PURE HATERADE.
>> WELL, MAYBE YOU CAN WIN
THE TROLL OVER.
>> YEAH.
"DAD, INAPPROPRIATE FORUM."
YOU WANNA HELP ME OUT WITH THIS
ONE, MAGGIE?
>> I GOT YOU.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT H8R.
>> OKAY.
>> announcer: CELEBRITIES.
YOU KNOW THEIR NAMES.
AND TALKING TRASH ABOUT THEM HAS
BECOME A GLOBAL PASTIME.
>> SNOOKI'S BIRTH WAS A HATE
CRIME TO ITALIANS.
>> announcer: THIS WEDNESDAY,
THE CW AND HOST MARIO LOPEZ
WILL BRING THE STARS AND THEIR
HATERS FACE-TO-FACE.
>> &l ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR &l
>> HEY.
>> YOU GOT A HATER.
YOU GOT A HATER.
>> WHAT ELSE IS NEW?
[laughs]
[camera shutters clicking]
>> I HATE KIM K.
THAT'S KIM KARDASHIAN.
I HATE HER ASS.
THAT ASS IS NOT REAL.
THIS IS REAL.
>> COME ON. I'M REALLY SHOCKED.
DID SHE SAY THAT?
>> WANNA KNOW WHY I HATE SNOOKI?
SHE'S NOT EVEN ITALIAN.
SHE'S FROM SANTIAGO, CHILE.
THANKS, CHILE.
>> IDIOT. I KNOW I'M NOT
ITALIAN.
>> [sighs] SHE SUCKS.
[camera shutters clicking]
>> SO DINA IS ACTUALLY DOING
YOGA RIGHT NOW.
>> HI. IS DINA HERE?
>> WE'RE GONNA SURPRISE HIM AT
A BAR WITH HIM AND HIS FRIENDS.
>> HELLO!
>> [gulps]
>> WHICH [bleep] IS NICK?
>> UM...
>> WHAT THE [bleep]?
>> WHAT DO YOU HAVE TO SAY TO
>> UM...
MY FACE?
>> WHAT DO YOU HAVE TO SAY TO
>> UM...
MY FACE?
>> [laughs]
>> UM...
>> &l THERE'S NOBODY LIKE ME &l
>> [laughs]
>> I DEFINITELY WANT TO INVITE
>> &l THERE'S NOBODY LIKE ME &l
THIS HATER AND HIS FAMILY TO
>> I DEFINITELY WANT TO INVITE
A NICE ITALIAN DINNER.
THIS HATER AND HIS FAMILY TO
>> I HEARD YOU PAINT.
A NICE ITALIAN DINNER.
MAYBE WE CAN GO TO A LOCAL
>> I HEARD YOU PAINT.
STUDIO.
MAYBE WE CAN GO TO A LOCAL
>> HEY, CHECK IT OUT.
STUDIO.
I'M YOU. I SHOULD BE ON
>> HEY, CHECK IT OUT.
JERSEY SHORE.
I'M YOU. I SHOULD BE ON
AH!
JERSEY SHORE.
WANNA MEET MY FAMILY?
AH!
HERE THEY ARE.
WANNA MEET MY FAMILY?
[ominous music]
HERE THEY ARE.
>> HELLO!
[ominous music]
[crickets chirping]
>> HELLO!
THIS IS DEFINITELY GONNA BE
[crickets chirping]
A CHALLENGE.
THIS IS DEFINITELY GONNA BE
>> I'D LOVE TO HAVE YOU JUDGE ME
A CHALLENGE.
OFF OF KNOWING ME INSTEAD OF
>> I'D LOVE TO HAVE YOU JUDGE ME
WHAT YOU WOULD PROBABLY THINK
OFF OF KNOWING ME INSTEAD OF
ABOUT ME.
WHAT YOU WOULD PROBABLY THINK
IF YOU'D SEEN THE SHOW, THEN YOU
ABOUT ME.
WOULD KNOW THAT WE ACTUALLY
IF YOU'D SEEN THE SHOW, THEN YOU
WENT TO NEW ORLEANS AND HELPED
WOULD KNOW THAT WE ACTUALLY
WITH HURRICANE KATRINA.
WENT TO NEW ORLEANS AND HELPED
I DO OTHER THINGS, LIKE IN
WITH HURRICANE KATRINA.
CHILDREN'S HOSPITALS AND OTHER
I DO OTHER THINGS, LIKE IN
COMMUNITIES.
CHILDREN'S HOSPITALS AND OTHER
>> I WAS JUST SHOCKED TO KNOW
COMMUNITIES.
THAT SHE'S DONE SOME GREAT
>> I WAS JUST SHOCKED TO KNOW
THINGS.
THAT SHE'S DONE SOME GREAT
>> YOU KNOW, MAYBE I REALLY DO
THINGS.
NEED TO CALM DOWN WITH,
>> YOU KNOW, MAYBE I REALLY DO
YOU KNOW, PARTYING AND STUFF
NEED TO CALM DOWN WITH,
LIKE THAT.
YOU KNOW, PARTYING AND STUFF
>> SURE. THIS IS VERY
LIKE THAT.
INTERESTING TO SEE THE SIDE OF
>> SURE. THIS IS VERY
YOU THAT WE DON'T GET TO SEE ON
INTERESTING TO SEE THE SIDE OF
TELEVISION.
YOU THAT WE DON'T GET TO SEE ON
>> YEAH.
TELEVISION.
>> HOW WOULD YOU LIKE IT IF WE
>> YEAH.
ALL CALLED YOU NICOLE TONIGHT?
>> HOW WOULD YOU LIKE IT IF WE
>> [gasps]
ALL CALLED YOU NICOLE TONIGHT?
>> INSTEAD OF SNOOKI.
>> [gasps]
>> THAT WOULD BE AMAZING.
>> INSTEAD OF SNOOKI.
>> YOU GOT IT, SNOOKI.
>> THAT WOULD BE AMAZING.
>> [scoffs]
>> YOU GOT IT, SNOOKI.
>> I HAD TO GET THE LAST ONE IN.
>> [scoffs]
SHE EARNS A LOT OF POINTS FOR
>> I HAD TO GET THE LAST ONE IN.
BEING ABLE TO COOK.
SHE EARNS A LOT OF POINTS FOR
>> I KNOW THAT EVERYTHING IS
BEING ABLE TO COOK.
NOT WHAT YOU SEE ON TV.
>> I KNOW THAT EVERYTHING IS
>> NICOLE'S PRETTY COOL.
NOT WHAT YOU SEE ON TV.
I GOTTA SAY, MY HAT'S OFF TO YA.
>> NICOLE'S PRETTY COOL.
>> WHOO!
I GOTTA SAY, MY HAT'S OFF TO YA.
>> FOR HER TO FACE ME AFTER
>> WHOO!
THE THINGS THAT I SAID,
>> FOR HER TO FACE ME AFTER
THAT'S COMMENDABLE.
THE THINGS THAT I SAID,
>> SO DO YOU STILL HATE ME?
THAT'S COMMENDABLE.
>> I AM NO LONGER A HATER.
>> SO DO YOU STILL HATE ME?
>> announcer: H8R.
>> I AM NO LONGER A HATER.
SERIES PREMIERE THIS WEDNESDAY
>> announcer: H8R.
AT 8:00, 7:00 CENTRAL ON THE CW.
SERIES PREMIERE THIS WEDNESDAY
>> H8R, A BOLD, NEW REALITY
AT 8:00, 7:00 CENTRAL ON THE CW.
SERIES, AIRS WEDNESDAYS THIS
>> H8R, A BOLD, NEW REALITY
FALL, FOLLOWED BY
SERIES, AIRS WEDNESDAYS THIS
AMERICA'S NEXT TOP MODEL,
FALL, FOLLOWED BY
ONLY ON THE CW.
AMERICA'S NEXT TOP MODEL,
>> THIS FALL,
ONLY ON THE CW.
AMERICA'S NEXT TOP MODEL KICKS
>> THIS FALL,
OFF ITS FIRST EVER ALL-STAR
AMERICA'S NEXT TOP MODEL KICKS
EDITION, PITTING PREVIOUS FAN
OFF ITS FIRST EVER ALL-STAR
FAVORITES AGAINST EACH OTHER
EDITION, PITTING PREVIOUS FAN
IN A BATTLE ROYALE.
FAVORITES AGAINST EACH OTHER
>> IT'S A HIGH-STAKES,
IN A BATTLE ROYALE.
HIGH-STRESS COMPETITION,
>> IT'S A HIGH-STAKES,
AND WE'LL GET AN INTIMATE LOOK
HIGH-STRESS COMPETITION,
AT THESE CONTESTANTS GET A
AND WE'LL GET AN INTIMATE LOOK
SECOND AND POSSIBLY LAST CHANCE
AT THESE CONTESTANTS GET A
AT THEIR DREAM.
SECOND AND POSSIBLY LAST CHANCE
>> I SMELL A CAT FIGHT.
>> announcer: WHAT HAPPENS WHEN
AMERICA'S NEXT TOP MODEL...
>> MY NAME IS LISA.
>> AND I'M 21 YEARS OLD.
>> AND I'M FROM HARLEM,
NEW YORK.
>> announcer: ASSEMBLES AN
ALL-STAR GROUP OF FAN FAVORITES
FROM THE PAST...
>> I'M GONNA TAKE THESE BITCHES
OUT.
THAT'S WHAT I'M GONNA DO.
>> announcer: A LITTLE BIT OF
MODELING...
>> I WAS BLOWN AWAY.
>> announcer: AND A WHOLE LOT
OF CRAZY.
>> I CAN BE VERY HIGH FASHION.
>> REOW.
>> DID SHE NOT SAY THAT?
>> YOU'RE THE ONE LYING.
>> SHUT UP.
>> announcer: IT'S NOT WHO MAKES
IT TO THE CATWALK...
>> ARE YOU FINISHED?
>> I'M FIGHTING FOR THIS.
>> announcer: IT'S WHO SURVIVES.
>> BETTER WATCH OUT, BECAUSE
I'M ONE NOT TO BE [bleep] WITH.
>> announcer: AMERICA'S NEXT
TOP MODEL: ALL-STARS.
PREMIERES THIS WEDNESDAY AT
9:00, 8:00 CENTRAL ON THE CW.
>> THE FIRST-EVER ALL-STAR
EDITION OF AMERICA'S TOP MODEL
AIRS WEDNESDAY FOLLOWING H8R,
ONLY ON THE CW.
>> I'M SO EXCITED.
STAY TUNED-- THE CW 2011 FALL
PREVIEW IS JUST HEATING UP.
>> IT'S GETTIN' HOT.
>> ANOTHER NEW SHOW TO LOOK OUT
FOR ON THE CW LATER THIS SEASON
IS REMODELED.
>> INDUSTRY VET PAUL FISHER
KNOWS WHAT IT TAKES TO CREATE
A SUPERMODEL, AND NOW HE'S
GIVING HIS KNOWLEDGE AND SOME
TOUGH LOVE TO SOME AGENCIES
AROUND THE WORLD WITH ONE GOAL--
CHANGE THE MODELING INDUSTRY
FOREVER.
>> LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
>> MY NAME IS PAUL FISHER.
I HAVE CREATED SOME OF THE
WORLD'S MOST FAMOUS SUPERMODELS.
GET ME VALERIE FROM VOGUE ON THE
PHONE--I WANNA HAVE A
CONVERSATION WITH HER.
I WAS A ROCK STAR IN THE
MODELING INDUSTRY.
SEX, DRUGS, POWER--I HAD IT ALL.
>> announcer: THE MAN WHO WALKED
AWAY AT THE TOP OF THE FASHION
BUSINESS...
>> MY LIFE SPUN OUT OF CONTROL,
AND I HAD TO GIVE IT ALL UP.
>> announcer: IS BACK WITH
A BRAND-NEW MISSION.
>> FOR 50 YEARS NOW, AGENCIES
AND SMALL MARKETS HAVE BEEN
FINDING AMAZING, AMAZING KIDS
AND GETTING SCREWED.
THE NEW YORK AGENCIES MAKE ALL
THE MONEY, THEY GET ALL THE
GLORY, AND THAT'S GONNA CHANGE.
AND I'M HERE TO PROTECT THE
LITTLE GUY.
BUT IF I'M GONNA TRANSFORM YOUR
AGENCY, WE'RE GONNA DO IT MY
WAY.
>> announcer: THE PLAN BEGINS
AT THE NETWORK...
>> THE NETWORK'S A COMMUNITY
OF MODELING AGENCIES FROM ALL
OVER THE WORLD.
>> announcer: WHERE EACH WEEK
THE CW WILL FOLLOW PAUL FISHER
AND HIS STAFF.
>> JOSEPH'S MY PERSONAL
ASSISTANT.
>> MONDAY MEETING, EVERYONE.
>> I WOULD NOT WISH THAT JOB
ON ANYBODY.
YOU TALKING TO ME?
WHERE'S MY CAR--GET MY CAR.
>> announcer: THEY'LL DEVELOP
A STRATEGY...
>> YOU KNOW WHAT WE'RE TRYING TO
DO HERE.
WE'RE CHANGING AN INDUSTRY.
>> announcer: TO TAKE ON TWO
SEPARATE BUT EQUALLY DAUNTING
TASKS.
JOB ONE--EXPAND HIS NETWORK OF
MODELING AGENCIES ONE SMALL
BOUTIQUE AT A TIME.
>> WOW.
YOU CANNOT LET PEOPLE WALK INTO
A PLACE THAT LOOKS LIKE THIS.
>> announcer: JOB TWO--DISCOVER
THE NEXT GENERATION OF
SUPERMODELS.
>> EACH AGENCY MUST FIND ONE
STAR.
THIS IS BROOK.
I'M GOING TO TURN THIS LITTLE
KID INTO THE NEXT GUESS MODEL.
>> announcer: WHILE HE REVAMPS
A BOUTIQUE TO JOIN HIS NETWORK.
>> THIS ARE WONDERFUL, WONDERFUL
PICTURES...FOR YOUR DORM ROOM.
>> announcer: HIS STAFF WILL
TRANSFORM AN UNKNOWN INTO A
STAR.
>> YOU GUYS ARE GONNA OVERSEE
THE BROOK PHOTO SHOOT AND
MAKEOVER.
DO NOT LET ME DOWN.
>> IF THIS DOESN'T HAPPEN, HE'S
GONNA KICK OUR ASSES.
>> I KNOW IT SOUNDS LIKE I'M
BEING A HARDASS.
I'M ACTUALLY DOING IT FROM A
PLACE OF LOVE.
SO FAR I'M SEEING URINE STAINS
ON THE FLOOR.
THE PLACE IS COMPLETELY
UNORGANIZED.
>> THERE'S NO AIR CONDITIONING.
I FELT LIKE I WAS IN SOMEONE'S
MOUTH THE WHOLE TIME.
>> IT STINKS!
DO YOU KNOW WHO THE [bleep]
I AM?
YOU'RE A FULL-SERVICE AGENCY
THAT IS NOT MAKING ANY MONEY!
>> I'M ECSTATIC SEEING SOMEONE
ELSE GET YELLED AT, 'CAUSE IT'S
NOT ME.
>> JOSEPH, I SEE PURPLE
ANYWHERE EVER AGAIN, FIRE THAT
PERSON.
>> SO PAUL, ARE YOU GONNA CHANGE
YOUR SHIRT?
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
>> IT'S PURPLE.
>> HOLY [bleep].
YOU'RE GONNA DO THIS FOR THE
NEXT 24 HOURS, AND YOU'RE GONNA
WORK YOUR [bleep] ASS OFF.
I'M GONNA MAKE THE HAIR BLOND.
I'M GONNA MAKE THE HAIR WHITE.
>> PAUL HAD A PARTICULAR VISION
FOR BROOK.
>> I'M SO EXCITED.
I'VE NEVER BEEN THIS EXCITED
FOR A SHOOT BEFORE.
>> THESE PHOTOS NEED TO MEET UP
TO PAUL'S STANDARDS.
>> SWEETHEART, THOSE ARE YOUR
MODELS.
WHY IS THAT OLD LADY RIGHT NEXT
TO THAT LITTLE KID?
THAT IS NOT A MODEL.
THAT'S NOT A MODEL.
THIS IS HOW YOU DESTROY MY
[bleep] REPUTATION.
THE PROPER AGE FOR A HIGH
FASHION MODEL--15 TO 18.
HOW OLD ARE YOU?
>> I'M 28.
>> YOU'RE OVER THE HILL AT 20.
MEN, 6 FEET TALL TO 6'2".
HOW TALL ARE YOU?
>> 5'10".
>> THE GIRLS ARE GONNA BE THE
SAME HEIGHT AS YOU.
>> I COULD HAVE BEEN A BETTER
MODEL THAN THEM, EVEN THOUGH I'M
LIKE ONE FOOT SHORTER THAN
EVERYONE ELSE.
>> BRING IN THE NEXT PERSON,
PLEASE.
SMILE FOR ME.
HOLY [bleep]!
SHE MAY HAVE JUST HAD A BRIEF
MEETING WITH A GUMMY BEAR!
MY PASSION GETS THE BEST OF ME.
BUT IT'S COMING FROM A PLACE OF
LOVE.
WE HAVE A LOT TO SHOW YOU.
THIS IS YOUR NEW OFFICE.
>> OH, WOW.
OVERNIGHT, THEY REDID MY ENTIRE
OFFICE.
>> I'M HOPING THAT THOSE ARE
TEARS OF JOY.
>> THEY ARE.
>> announcer: COMING SOON TO THE
CW...
>> TAKE A LOOK AT YOUR NEW
MODELS--THESE ARE THE PEOPLE
YOU TAKE CARE OF NOW.
YOU THINK I WAS GONNA LET YOU
DOWN?
YOU THINK I'M GONNA LET YOU
WE CAN ACTUALLY MAKE THEIR
DOWN?
DREAMS COME TRUE.
WE CAN ACTUALLY MAKE THEIR
>> announcer: PAUL FISHER WILL
DREAMS COME TRUE.
BUILD A NEW MODELING NETWORK
>> announcer: PAUL FISHER WILL
FROM THE GROUND UP.
BUILD A NEW MODELING NETWORK
WE'RE GOING TO CREATE STARS
FROM THE GROUND UP.
TOGETHER, I PROMISE YOU.
WE'RE GOING TO CREATE STARS
>> ALL THESE BEAUTIFUL PEOPLE
TOGETHER, I PROMISE YOU.
ARE NOW MY NEW FACES.
>> ALL THESE BEAUTIFUL PEOPLE
>> WE MET A POTENTIAL STAR--
ARE NOW MY NEW FACES.
SHAUNESSY.
>> WE MET A POTENTIAL STAR--
>> announcer: AND HE'LL
SHAUNESSY.
INTRODUCE THE WORLD TO HIS NEXT
>> announcer: AND HE'LL
WAVE OF SUPERMODELS.
INTRODUCE THE WORLD TO HIS NEXT
>> OH, MY GOD, YOU GUYS, THIS IS
WAVE OF SUPERMODELS.
THE CREATION OF A STAR.
>> OH, MY GOD, YOU GUYS, THIS IS
BUT SHE'S NOT READY FOR NEW
THE CREATION OF A STAR.
YORK, AND YOU KNOW WHO IS,
BUT SHE'S NOT READY FOR NEW
RIGHT?
YORK, AND YOU KNOW WHO IS,
SHAUNESSY.
RIGHT?
>> I SHOULD BE IN SCHOOL RIGHT
SHAUNESSY.
NOW, BUT I CANNOT BELIEVE THAT
>> I SHOULD BE IN SCHOOL RIGHT
I'M IN NEW YORK CITY.
NOW, BUT I CANNOT BELIEVE THAT
>> BOOKING A JOB WITH ANDY
I'M IN NEW YORK CITY.
HILFIGER WOULD PUT SHAUNESSY
>> BOOKING A JOB WITH ANDY
ON THE MAP.
HILFIGER WOULD PUT SHAUNESSY
>> PAUL, THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR
ON THE MAP.
EVERYTHING THAT YOU'VE DONE FOR
>> PAUL, THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR
ME.
EVERYTHING THAT YOU'VE DONE FOR
>> WE'RE GOING TO TRANSFORM
ME.
THEIR AGENCIES, TEACH THEM HOW
>> WE'RE GOING TO TRANSFORM
TO RUN THEIR BUSINESS, AND SHOW
THEIR AGENCIES, TEACH THEM HOW
THEM HOW TO CREATE STARS.
TO RUN THEIR BUSINESS, AND SHOW
>> announcer: THE FASHION
THEM HOW TO CREATE STARS.
INDUSTRY IS ABOUT TO GET...
>> announcer: THE FASHION
REMODELED.
INDUSTRY IS ABOUT TO GET...
NEW REALITY SERIES COMING SOON
REMODELED.
TO THE CW.
NEW REALITY SERIES COMING SOON
>> WHEW! WE JUST COVERED SOME
TO THE CW.
GROUND, FOLKS.
>> WHEW! WE JUST COVERED SOME
THAT WAS SOME HEART-POUNDING
GROUND, FOLKS.
ENTERTAINMENT.
THAT WAS SOME HEART-POUNDING
>> AND BEST OF ALL, NO ONE GOT
ENTERTAINMENT.
HURT.
>> AND BEST OF ALL, NO ONE GOT
CW IS LOOKING GOOD THIS FALL.
HURT.
>> IT'S FIVE GREAT NIGHTS OF
CW IS LOOKING GOOD THIS FALL.
ALL-NEW, ORIGINAL PROGRAMMING,
>> IT'S FIVE GREAT NIGHTS OF
STARTING WITH GOSSIP GIRL
ALL-NEW, ORIGINAL PROGRAMMING,
AND HART OF DIXIE ON MONDAYS.
STARTING WITH GOSSIP GIRL
>> 90210 AND RINGER ON TUESDAYS.
AND HART OF DIXIE ON MONDAYS.
>> THE ALL-NEW REALITY SHOW H8R
>> 90210 AND RINGER ON TUESDAYS.
AND THE PUMPED-UP ALL-STAR
>> THE ALL-NEW REALITY SHOW H8R
EDITION OF AMERICA'S NEXT TOP
AND THE PUMPED-UP ALL-STAR
MODEL ON WEDNESDAYS.
EDITION OF AMERICA'S NEXT TOP
>> THE VAMPIRE DIARIES
MODEL ON WEDNESDAYS.
AND THE SECRET CIRCLE
>> THE VAMPIRE DIARIES
ON THURSDAYS.
AND THE SECRET CIRCLE
>> AND NIKITA AND SUPERNATURAL
ON THURSDAYS.
ON FRIDAYS.
>> AND NIKITA AND SUPERNATURAL
>> AN ENTIRE WEEK OF ORIGINAL
ON FRIDAYS.
PROGRAMMING, ALL-NEW AND ONLY
>> AN ENTIRE WEEK OF ORIGINAL
ON THE CW.
PROGRAMMING, ALL-NEW AND ONLY
>> WE HOPE THAT YOU'VE ENJOYED
ON THE CW.
THIS SNEAK PEEK.
>> WE HOPE THAT YOU'VE ENJOYED
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
THIS SNEAK PEEK.
>> WE WILL SEE YOU THIS FALL.
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
>> [clicks tongue]
Captioning by CaptionMax
www.captionmax.com